MOHD IZWAN **MD RAZI**



No 50 taman permatang katong,Kota Kuala Muda, Kedah

+013-4476026

WHY ME?

A confident and have self-motivated, self-sufficent and comes to you with a strong background in counseling. Able to worked in under pressure, and has a comprehensive understanding of photoshop, microsoft office and the latest social media.. Besides, believe in teamwork.. Also I am quick learner and great team player.

SKILLS

Teamwork
Communication
Leadership
Ms Excel
Ms Word
Ms Powerpoint
Adobe Photoshop

LANGUAGES

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2016 - present

HEIGHTS

ASIST. MANAGER
OLDTOWN WHITE COFFEE , LAGENDA

Management in store

🛡 , Sungai Petani, Kedah

Nov 2015 -Apr 2016

Operato

Able Glory Sdn Bhd,Lot 17 Bakar Arang Industrial Estate

Worked on production, achieve the target

Sungai Petani, Kedah

Feb 2015 – Jun 2015

Internship Counsellor

Pusat Kaunseling ,Jabatan Hal Ehwal Pelajar ,Universiti Utara Malaysia

Worked directly with clients (student), counseling sessions, admin, Talk, social media

Sintok, Kedah

Jan 2011 – Aug 2011

Storekeeper/warehouse

Ranbaxy Sdn Bhd, Sungai Petani

. Worked on store and prepared ordering ,checked the product before deliver out the store.

Sp, Kedah

EDUCATION

2011 - 2015

Counselling

Bachelor's Degree

Relevant Coursework: Statistics, Mental Health, Human Resourses Development, Theory Counselling, Cumulative GPA: 3.10

▼ UNIVERSITY OF MALAYA , KL

2009 - 2010

Sijil Tinggi Pelajaran Malaysia (STPM)

SMK Kota Kuala Muda

Gpa : 2.67

KEDAH

Mac 2016

Takaful Basic Examination (TBE)
Certificate

Certification from IBFIM

KL

REFERENCE

DR. IDA HARTINA

Pensyarah

Fakulti Pendidikan Universiti Malaya 50603 Kuala Lumpur. 03-79675063/0122195755

UM, KL